Which of the following is not valid with reference to MPI ?


Select one:
a. All parallelism is implicit
b. The programming model is a distributed memory model
c. MPI - Comm - Size returns the total number of MPI processes in specified communication
d. MPI can run on any hardware platform
A


Describe the parameter tag in the following function call:
MPI_Recv(message, 4, MPI_CHAR, 5, tag, MPI_COMM_WORLD, &status)
Select one:
a. The message type of the incoming message
b. The type of the process group
c. A user-assigned number that must match on both sender and receiver
d. Type of communication method
c


For the MPI program to run on 8 distributed machines with 1024KB of data to be send to each machines. How you can run the MPI program for the above mention case.
Select one:
a. mpirun –np 8 ./a.out
b. mpirun np 4 a.out
c. mpirun –np = 8 ./a.out
d. mpirun –np = 4 a.out
a


Which of the following is not valid with reference to MPI ?
Select one:
a. All parallelism is implicit
b. MPI - Comm - Size returns the total number of MPI processes in specified communication
c. The programming model is a distributed memory model
d. MPI can run on any hardware platform
a


What is the relationship between Warps, thread blocks, and CUDA cores?
Select one:
a. warp is decided by the GPU, and each thread block executes on a single CUDA core
b. thread block may be divided into a number of warps, and each warp may execute on a single CUDA core
c. warp is divided into a number of thread blocks, and each thread block executes on a single CUDA core
d. thread block is assigned to a warp, and each thread in the warp is executed on a separate CUDA core
B


Hybrid programming combines what two models of computing?
Select one:
a. All of these
b. Parallel and serial
c. Shared-memory parallel and distributed-memory parallel
d. Message-passing and NUMA
c


Which of the following is not a form of parallelism supported by CUDA
Select one:
a. Data parallelism - Different threads and blocks process different parts of data in memory
b. Thread level task parallelism - Different threads execute a different tasks
c. Block and grid level parallelism - Different blocks or grids execute different tasks
d. Vector parallelism - Floating point computations are executed in parallel on wide vector units
D


Which of the following is incorrect about MPI:
Select one:
a. You can compile your MPI code using any MPI implementation, running on your architecture
b. MPI functions are standardized, which means function calls behave the same regardless of which implementation is used
c. MPI uses a shared memory programming model, which means all processes can access shared memory
d. Any MPI process can directly send and receive messages, to and from other processes
c


How the Page-Locked Host Memory is allocated at the time of program execution. Identify the correct command to allocate and release the host memory.
Select one:
a. cudaHostAlloc() and cudaHostFree()
b. cudaHostAlloc() and cudaFreeHost()
c. cudaHostMalloc() and cudaHostFree()
d. cudaMallocHost() and cudaFreeHost()


What does MPI_COMM_RANK return?
Select one:
a. Numerical identifier of the current process within an MPI communicator
b. Linux process ID
c. Number of processes in an MPI program
d. Priority of the current process
a


Which of the following is not a form of parallelism supported by CUDA
Select one:
a. Data parallelism - Different threads and blocks process different parts of data in memory
b. Thread level task parallelism - Different threads execute a different tasks
c. Block and grid level parallelism - Different blocks or grids execute different tasks
d. Vector parallelism - Floating point computations are executed in parallel on wide vector units
D


Which of the following architecture is/are not suitable for realizing SIMD?
Veu neuman
Von Neumann



Which of the following statements is not true?
Select one:
a. MPI_lsend and MPI_Irecv are non-blocking message passing routines of MPI
b. MPI_Ssend and MPI_Bsend are blocking message passing routines of MPI
c. MPI_lssend and MPI_Ibsend are non-blocking message passing routines of MPI
d. MPI_Send and MPI_Recv are non-blocking message passing routines of MPI


Which of the following is incorrect about MPI:
Select one:
a. MPI functions are standardized, which means function calls behave the same regardless of which implementation is used
b. Any MPI process can directly send and receive messages, to and from other processes
c. MPI uses a shared memory programming model, which means all processes can access shared memory
d. You can compile your MPI code using any MPI implementation, running on your architecture
C


What does MPI_COMM_RANK return?
Select one:
a. Priority of the current process
b. Number of processes in an MPI program
c. Linux process ID
d. Numerical identifier of the current process within an MPI communicator
D


What purpose does a communicator serve?
Select one:
a. All of these
b. If equal to MPI_COMM_WORLD, it shows that the communication involves all processes
c. It can be used to identify a subgroup of processes that will participate in message passing
d. It prevents your main program’s MPI calls from being confused with a library’s MPI calls


Hybrid programming combines what two models of computing?
Select one:
a. Shared-memory parallel and distributed-memory parallel
b. Parallel and serial
c. All of these
d. Message-passing and NUMA
A


Moving data in a distributed memory system is done with message-passing libraries such as MPI. Is it a good idea to use collective communication instead of point to point communication whenever possible?
Select one:
a. None of these
b. Both statements
c. MPI can use broadcast algorithms optimized for the specific architecture
d. all collective communication functions are blocking which can increase synchronization overhead, while the programmer can choose between blocking and non-blocking point to point functions depending on the circumstances
D

For the MPI program to run on 8 distributed machines with 1024KB of data to be send to each machines. How you can run the MPI program for the above mention case.
Select one:
a. mpirun –np = 4 a.out
b. mpirun –np = 8 ./a.out
c. mpirun –np 8 ./a.out
d. mpirun np 4 a.out


Which of the following statements is not true?

Select one:
a. MPI_Send and MPI_Recv are non-blocking message passing routines of MPI
b. MPI_lsend and MPI_Irecv are non-blocking message passing routines of MPI
c. MPI_Ssend and MPI_Bsend are blocking message passing routines of MPI
d. MPI_lssend and MPI_Ibsend are non-blocking message passing routines of MPI
a

Moving data in a distributed memory system is done with message-passing libraries such as MPI. Is it a good idea to use collective communication instead of point to point communication whenever possible?

Select one:
a. all collective communication functions are blocking which can increase synchronization overhead, while the programmer can choose between blocking and non-blocking point to point functions depending on the circumstances
b. MPI can use broadcast algorithms optimized for the specific architecture
c. Both statements
d. None of these


What purpose does a communicator serve?
Select one:
a. All of these
b. If equal to MPI_COMM_WORLD, it shows that the communication involves all processes
c. It prevents your main program’s MPI calls from being confused with a library’s MPI calls
d. It can be used to identify a subgroup of processes that will participate in message


What is the relationship between Warps, thread blocks, and CUDA cores?

Select one:
a. warp is divided into a number of thread blocks, and each thread block executes on a single CUDA core
b. warp is decided by the GPU, and each thread block executes on a single CUDA core
c. thread block is assigned to a warp, and each thread in the warp is executed on a separate CUDA core
d. thread block may be divided into a number of warps, and each warp may execute on a single CUDA core.
d

Select one:
a. compared to CPU, GPUs have larger register file, smaller L1/L2 cache with higher bandwidth
b. cache + constant memory is unified foe all SMs
c. L1 and L2 cache + shared memory is private to SMs
d. compared to CPU, GPUs have smaller register file, smaller L1/L2 cache with lower bandwidth
c



